(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T00:00:15.048171",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ここはねぼらぼ学園！
This is Nepolabo Academy!
部活もクラスも違うけど、ねねたち同じ学生寮に住んでるんだ！
Our clubs and classes are different, but we all live in the same dorm!
ふざけて、笑って、時々喧嘩して！
Goofing off, laughing, fighting sometimes...
でも集まると…なんか落ち着く！
...but when we're together, it feels comforting!
今日も談話室は賑やか。
The common room is lively again today.
誰かの声が聞こえるだけで、安心するんだよね。
Just hearing someone's voice puts me at ease.
この場所で私達だけの学寮生活を作るなんて…
Creating our very own dorm life here...
楽しそうでワクワクする！
...sounds so fun and exciting!
さあ！
Now!
私たちの！
Our...
輝く青春が…
...shining youth...
始まる！
...begins!
ねぼらぼ学園！5周年記念！輝く学祭！
Nepolabo Academy! 5th Anniversary Special! Shining School Festival!
今日は学祭！生徒会が中心になって開催する、夏の一大イベント！
Today is the school festival! A major summer event hosted mainly by the student council!
会長からの頼みで、急遽ねぼらぼで出し物を考えることになったんだけど――
At the student council president's request, Nepolabo was suddenly asked to plan a performance...
何も考えられてなーーーい！！！！
...but we haven't thought of ANYTHING!!!!
やばいよ…気づいたら、もう当日だよ～～～！
This is bad... Before we knew it, it's already the day of the event!
だから言ったじゃん！もっと早く集まって決めようって！
That's why I told you! We should've gotten together earlier to decide!
いや〜何とかなるって思ってたんだけどな〜（笑）
Well, I honestly thought it would work out somehow, haha!
うう…これはマズい…変なことやったら、会長になんて言われるか……
Ugh... This is bad... If we mess up, who knows what the president will say...
はぁ……
Haaah...
よしっ、断ろう！！
Alright, let's decline!!
やめなー！当日に断れるわけないでしょ！
Stop it! There's no way we can cancel on the day of!
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミちゃんならきっと許してくれるって♪
It's okay, it's okay! I'm sure Lamy-chan will forgive us!
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミィちゃんならきっと許してくれるって♪
"Don't worry, Lamy-chan will surely forgive us♪"
なんでラミィだけ謝る前提なのよ！
"Why are you assuming only Lamy has to apologize?!"
...いや、まだ終わってない！！学景祭はお昼から... ほんのちょっとだけ、まだ時間はある！
"...No, it's not over yet!! The festival starts at noon... We still have a little bit of time!"
よし、とりあえず案を出してみよっか～
"Alright, let's brainstorm some ideas for now~"
学校の祭りといえば... 焼きそば、じゃがバター、唐揚げ、クレープ、ポテト...
"When you think of school festivals... Yakisoba, buttered potatoes, fried chicken, crepes, fries..."
食べ物しかないじゃん！！
"It's all food!!"
...でも今から仕込みはちょっと無理かもね
"...But preparing food from scratch now might be impossible."
まあできるとしたら 炎天下でカラカラな喉に染み渡る... ラミィ水！！ これは売れるぞ～
"Well, if there's anything we can do... Lamy Water, to quench parched throats in the scorching heat!! This is gonna sell~"
やめろぉぉぉ！！！
"Stop ittt!!!"
うっひょ～お！ しぼり出して～
"Whew~! Squeeze it out~"
バカなこと言ってないで！もっと真面目に考えなさいって！
"Stop saying stupid things! Think more seriously!"
そんなに言うならラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
"If you say so, what do you want to do, Lamy-chan?"
ラミィ？ そうだなあ... やっぱ歌は歌いたいし... バンドとか、かな？
"Me? Well... I still want to sing... Maybe a band or something?"
ふつう
"Boring."
ひねりがな～い
"No twist at all~"
......っツ（笑）
"...(snicker)"
こいつら...！
"These guys...!"
でもまあ、歌はいいかもね～
"But well, singing might be good~"
ショート動画用にいろいろな曲練習してるし その中から何かやってみる？
"We've been practicing various songs for short videos anyway, so why don't we try performing one of those?"
じゃあねね、あれやりたい！！ 元気いっぱいの、ねねたちにピッタリなやつ！！
"Then Nene wants to do THAT one!! The super energetic one that's perfect for us!!"
あ～～あれね！
"Ahhh, that one!"
いいんじゃない！
"Sounds good!"
じゃ、とりあえずやってみますか！
"Alright, then shall we give it a try?"
キメマスター！！
"Kime Master!!"
前人ゼロの未踏地だよなぁ (そいやー！)
"It's an uncharted land with zero predecessors! (Soiya!)"
生まれ変わる一歩目は 一歩目が大事さ 恐れないよ
"The first step to transforming yourself... That first step is crucial, don't be afraid"
何度でも平気な顔で走り出して 行かなきゃ！上々の気分さ
"Start running again and again with a cool face! Got to go! Feelin' great"
やってみたいことには欲張りだね 欲張りごめんね 直さないよ
"Greedy for things we wanna try! Sorry for being greedy, won't change it"
何度でも未来を書き換えたくなるのさ 行かなきゃ！最高の仲間と
"Makes you wanna rewrite the future over and over! Got to go! With the best crew"
星になろうよ 輝きたいよ 今は今だけ (後悔しないようにねっ)
"Let's become stars, wanna shine! Right now, just right now (So we don't have regrets)"
さぁおいで MONSTERS
"Come on over, MONSTERS"
踊れば MONSTERS
"If we dance, MONSTERS"
こんなにも無敵 PIKA STARS!
"So completely invincible, PIKA STARS!"
夢が KIRA-KIRA 無駄に KIRA-KIRA？？
"Dreams are KIRA-KIRA, excessively KIRA-KIRA??"
前進だ DOKA-DOKA！！
"Charge ahead, DOKA-DOKA!!"
はわっ 通りまーす！
"Hawatt, passing through~!"
キまっちゃってる！？
"Are we totally locked in?!"
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制限はね無視だよ
"Full speed mode, yo-ho-ho! Ignore all limits"
なんでもかんでもやっぱっぱ 全力がいいよね
"Anything and everything, after all, full power is best"
笑顔あり キメ顔あり 最強 BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！ (チェストー！)
"Smiles on, cool faces on! Aim for the strongest BIG BANG future! (Chesto~!)"
手とりあったらるんったった 怖くはないよね
"Hand in hand, tra-la-la, it's not scary at all"
夢の計測メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
"The dream measurement meter is about to max out"
地球からやってきたボクらは 本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
"We who came from Earth are heading forward today too! Go ahead! Go ahead!"
怒られるまで？ 怒られても止まれ無いのです (騒々しくてもごめんなさーい！)
"Until we get scolded? Even if scolded, we can't be stopped! (Sorry for being noisy~!)"
先陣誰だい？ ボクらだい！
"Who's leading the charge? We are!"
いわゆる前人ゼロの未踏地だよなぁ (そいやー！)
"The so-called uncharted land with zero predecessors! (Soiya!)"
ゆずらないないない百歩目も 百歩ゆずるなんて負けよ駄目よ
"Won't give up even a hundred steps! Giving an inch is defeat, no way"
ゴールへのロードは砂利と岩だらけで 泣いても顔は “に・や・り”
"The road to the goal is full of gravel and rocks, even if crying, our face wears a grin"
そんな時あきらめ悪く進め だってほらあきらめたくない夢が
"At times like that, persistently press on! Because look, there's a dream we won't give up on"
進化してみんなを果ての果ての空へ 連れ去るボクら地球女子
"Evolving to carry everyone to the furthest sky, us Earth girls"
憧れたんだ 星の光は 消えないときめき (心拍数上がりまくりっ)
"We longed for it, star's light is an everlasting thrill (Heart rate soaring up)"
さぁ跳んで MONSTERS
"Come on, jump, MONSTERS"
暴れちゃお MONSTERS
"Let's go wild, MONSTERS"
だいたんで無敵 PIKA STARS! 随時きらめきが上昇中 つまり好調中
"Bold and invincible PIKA STARS! Sparkle rising continuously, meaning in top condition"
あ、サビきまーす
"Ah, chorus coming up~"
多分勝利は、キまっちゃってる！！ (いいとこだったのにー！)
"Victory is probably locked in!! (Right at the best part, too~!)"
バンドじゃないからせっせっせ カッコつけなければ
"Not a band, so gotta work hard to look cool"
バンドじゃないからよいよいよい カッコがつくのだよ
"Not a band, so yo-yo-yo, that's what makes it look cool"
バカ騒ぎ やんちゃ騒ぎ やったもん勝ち 狙っちゃえ未来！ (チェストー！)
"Wild noise, mischievous fun, winner takes all, aim for the future! (Chesto~!)"
銀河のどっかの頂点に旗を立てるまで
"Until we plant a flag at the peak of somewhere in the galaxy"
ニューなレコードの更新は続くんだってば
"Updating new records keeps on going, I tell ya"
地球からやってきたボクらよ やりまくれ Go ahead! Go ahead!
"We who came from Earth! Go all out, Go ahead! Go ahead!"
さあ次の星へ！
"Now onto the next star!"
一歩が百歩の始まりだから行こうよ すぐに行こうよ
"Because one step is the start of a hundred, let's go, let's go right away"
無理は道理よりも強引だなー 瞬間をキミと一緒にね
"Unreasonable forces overrule reason~ Spending this moment with you"
真っ暗な空かもしれないけどボクらは輝きたい お目々を開いてお目々を離すなよー？
"It might be a pitch-black sky, but we wanna shine! Open your eyes and don't look away~?"
もんスター！ もんスター！ もんスター！
"Monster! Monster! Monster!"
前人未踏の宇宙に全速の全力でGOだyeah！！
"Into the uncharted universe, GO with full speed and full power, yeah!!"
楽観だい そうだそうだった
"Optimistic, right, that's how it was!"
楽観的 そうだそうだっ
Optimistic! That's right, that's right!
地球はブルーだブルーだっ
Earth is blue, it's blue!
ぜんぶを欲しがれ EARTHっ子！
Want everything, Earth kids!
全開かい そうかもそうかもっ
Full speed ahead? Maybe so, maybe so!
宇宙のスターにスターに
A star in the universe, a star...
なりたい？ / なりたい
Want to become? / I want to become...
なれそう？なれそうだよ！
Can we? Looks like we can!
キマッチッたしね！
We're all set!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制限はね無視だよ
Full speed mode, heave-ho! Ignore the limits!
なんでもかんでもやっぱっぱ 全力がいいよね
Everything, after all, going all out is best!
笑顔終わり 日替わり
Ending with a smile, changing daily...
最強BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！
Strongest BIG BANG, target the future!
チェストー！
Chest!
手とりあったらるんたった 怖くはないよね
Holding hands, tra-la-la, it's not scary!
夢の計測メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
The meter measuring dreams is about to overflow!
地球から やっできたボクらは
We who came from Earth...
本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
Go ahead today as well! Go ahead!
怒られるまで？
Until we get scolded?
･･･怒られても止まれないのです
...Even if scolded, we can't stop.
最後の最後もごめんなさーい！
To the very, very end, sorry!
先陣誰だい？ ボクらだい！
Who's taking the lead? We are!
いわゆる前人ゼロの未踏地だよなあ
An unexplored territory with zero predecessors, huh?
もう一回！
One more time!
大いなる一歩さ ボクらと最高速で
A giant step, at top speed with us!
前人ゼロの未踏地へ Go！！
Go to the unexplored land with zero predecessors!!
そいやー！
Soiyaa!
よ〜っし次はバンドだ！ できる曲を片っ端からやっていこう〜〜！！
"Alright, next up is the band! Let's play every song we can!!"
でもわたしたち、楽器できなくない……？
"But wait... aren't we unable to play instruments...?"
こういうのはね、雰囲気が大事！ 頑張ってる姿を見せれば、それでOK！
"You see, with things like this, the mood is key! If you show them you're trying hard, that's enough!"
バカにしておいて結局やるのね…
"Making fun of it, but in the end you're still going along..."
じゃあまず、誰が何やるか決めよう〜！ ねねはギターっ！！
"Alright then, first let's decide who plays what! Nene is on guitar!!"
じゃあししろんはドラムかな〜
"Well then, Shishiron will probably do drums~"
ポルカはベースで〜！
"Polka is on bass~!"
じゃあラミィは…シンセ、やろうかなっ
"Then I guess Lamy will play synth!"
そうしたら演出も考えないとな〜
"In that case, we also gotta plan the stage performance~"
派手にドカーンってしたい！！
"I wanna do a huge, flashy explosion!!"
ざっくりだな〜
"That's pretty vague~"
サビにキャノンとか出す？
"Should we fire off cannons during the chorus?"
いいね！ 照明もレーザー出したりしてピカピカにしていこう！
"Nice! Let's make the lights flash with lasers and stuff too!"
じゃあ、ねねはポルカと動き回ってパフォーマンスしよう！
"Then Nene and Polka will move all around and perform!"
やるやるっ！任せて〜！！
"Count me in! Leave it to me~!!"
だ、大丈夫かな？ 間に合わなくってアタフタするんじゃない？
"I-Is this really okay? Won't we end up flustered and running out of time?"
まぁ、それも”わたし達らしさ”ってことで〜
"Well, that's just being ourselves too~"
ノリでなんとかなるなる！
"We'll make it work with good energy!"
…あ、そうだ、バンド名、どうするの？
"...Ah, right, what about our band name?"
えっ！かっこいいやつがいい〜！！
"Eh! I want something really cool~!!"
じゃあ 「青春★ピチピチフルスロットル団！！」
"Then 'Youth ★ Lively Full Throttle Group!!'"
…だ、ださっ!?!?
"...Th-That's so lame!?!?"
もうちょい5期生要素も入れ we want to add 5th gen elements. ラーメン、芝刈り機、低気圧……
"I want to add a bit more 5th gen elements too. Ramen, lawnmower, low pressure..."
「カブトムシ」って入れたらかっこいいよ！！
"Adding 'Rhinoceros Beetle' would make it so cool!!"
「青春低気圧★ラーメンピチピチフルスロットル芝刈り機団！！」
"'Youth Low Pressure ★ Ramen Lively Full Throttle Lawnmower Group!!'"
混ぜるな！ぐちゃぐちゃだよぉ…
"Don't mix them together! It's total chaos..."
じゃあラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
"Then Lamy-chan, what would you like?"
え〜やっぱり可愛いのがいいかなぁ〜 「ねぼらぼハーモニー♪」とか〜♪
"Hmm... as expected, I'd prefer something cute~ Like 'NeBoLaBo Harmony♪'~♪"
それでいいのかラミィ
"Are you really fine with that, Lamy?"
かっこよくないよラミィ
"That's not cool at all, Lamy."
俺、恥ずかしいよラミィ
"Man, I'm embarrassed, Lamy."
ほんっとに……お前らっ！！
"Seriously... you guys!!"
よ〜〜し！バンド名も決まったし、やってみますか〜！！
"Alright! Now that we have a band name, shall we give it a try~!!"
これで、学僚祭の注目はいただきだーっ！！
"With this, all eyes at the school festival will be on us!!"
えっ！？あれでいくの！？
"Huh!? We're actually going with that!?"
いくぞーっ！！よ〜いっ！
"Here we go!! Get ready!"
どん！！！
"Bang!!!"
走って 走って 憧れを越えて
Run, run, surpassing admiration!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
まだ見たことのないスピードの向こう側へ
Towards the other side of a speed yet unseen!
ウォームアップは完璧さ！
The warm-up is perfect!
地球をほら 踏み込む蹄鉄
Look, horseshoes stomping upon the Earth!
ゴール前のキセキ
The miracle before the goal line!
仕掛ける場所は最終コーナー
The place to make our move is the final corner!
あとは 行けるところまで息を切らせてたい
After that, I want to run breathless as far as I can go!
何万と手を叩くオーディエンス 割れんばかり響く大歓声
Tens of thousands of audience members clapping hands, deafening cheers echoing out!
ファンファーレが鳴る
The fanfare sounds!
心音が高まる
Our heartbeats quicken!
動き出す秒針 夢のゲートが開く
The second hand starts moving, the gate of dreams opens!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
走って 走って 憧れを追い越して
Run, run, passing beyond admiration!
次は誰の番だ！？
Whose turn is next!?
さあ目指すはスーパー…
Now, aiming for the super...
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Come on, aiming for superstar!
生きてく
Living...
意味なんて
...what purpose...
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
...will follow after leaving everyone behind!
勝ちたい！
I want to win!
そうこれは本能
Yes, this is instinct!
走りたい！
I want to run!
止まない衝動
An unstoppable impulse!
叫びたい！
I want to shout!
勝利の雄叫びを
A shout of victory!
轟け！
Resonate!
誰かとバチバチ競うことでしか
Only by fiercely competing with someone
到達し得ない輝かしいゴールライン
can you reach the brilliant goal line!
AH どんな
Ah, no matter what...
理屈でも言語化できない感情
...emotions can't be put into logic or words!
科学を超えて
Beyond science!
ざっと超えて
Way beyond!
熱い勝負したい したい したい
I wanna have an intense battle, wanna, wanna!
どちらが最強か
Which one is the strongest?
決めよう好敵手
Let's decide, rival!
速い者が勝つ 何も言い訳はなしだ
The fastest wins, no excuses allowed!
よーいどん！
Ready, set, go!
飛ばして 飛ばして
Blast off, blast off!
涙さえ振り切って
Shaking off even tears,
前に足を出すんだ 悩む暇なんてない
Step forward, there's no time to hesitate!
答えを出すのは
Finding the answer...
ゴールした後でも遅くない
...isn't too late even after crossing the goal!
抗え本能
Resist, instinct!
絶好！
Perfect shape!
譲れない頂上
An unyielding summit!
騒ぎたい！
I wanna make some noise!
王者の雄叫びに
To the champion's roar,
続け！
follow!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
どんなことが起こったって
No matter what happens,
レースが止まらないように
so that the race doesn't stop,
ずっと続いていくこの友情
this friendship that continues forever...
憎まれ口を叩いたって
Even if we talk tough to each other,
みんな一列になれば
once we all line up,
AH てっぺんめがけて
Ah, aiming for the top...
位置についてよーい
On your marks, get set...
走って 走って
Run, run!
憧れ追い越して
Surpassing our admiration,
次は誰の番だ
whose turn is next?
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Come on, aiming for superstar!
生きてく
Living...
意味なんて
...what purpose...
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
...will follow after leaving everyone behind!
勝ちたい！
I want to win!
そうこれは本能
Yes, this is instinct!
走りたい！
I want to run!
止まない衝動
An unstoppable impulse!
叫びたい！
I want to shout!
勝利の雄叫びよ
A shout of victory!
轟け！
Resonate!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
ひゃあああ〜っ！！冷たーいっ！！
Hyaaa! It's so cold!
バンドして汗かいちゃったからね〜 リフレッシュ、リフレッシュ♪
We worked up a sweat during the band performance~ Time to refresh, refresh♪
ほら、おまるんも早く進んで〜！！
Come on, Omarun, hurry up and move ahead~!!
ああああああ〜〜〜〜っ 地獄シャワー 無理〜〜〜！！！
Aahhhhhhh! Hellish shower, no way~!!!
シャワー浴びて、プールで泳いで遊んだら… きっといいアイデアも出てくるってばぁ！
Once we take a shower and play in the pool... I'm sure we'll get some great ideas!
…そう言って、毎回遊び疲れて終わるんだけどね〜〜
...You always say that, but every time we just end up getting worn out from playing~~
でもさ！夏といえばプールでしょ！ここで何かするのもアリじゃない？
But hey! Summer means the pool! Wouldn't it be great to do something here?
プールでできることといえば…… 撮影会！！
When you think of things to do at the pool... A photo shoot!!
ねねたちの水着姿で！
Featuring us in our swimsuits!
お客さんを…… 瞬殺♡
Instantly knocking out... the audience♡
ダメに決まってるだろ！！ 会長に怒られるよっ！！
Of course that's a no-go!! The president will scold us!!
絶対に盛り上がるのにな〜〜
Man, it would definitely be a hit though~~
……プールにラミィちゃん沈めて 産地直送ラミィ水……これは売れる！！
...Submerge Lamy-chan in the pool to get farm-fresh Lamy Water... This will sell!!
そこっ！ラミィから出汁とろうとするな！ラミィ水は忘れろ！！
Hey, you! Don't try to extract broth from Lamy! Forget about Lamy Water!!
…じゃあ、ライブしとく？ プールサイドで！
...Then how about we do a live show? By the poolside!
まぁ〜そうなるよね〜！ でも夏、プール、歌…最高にマッチしてるっ！
Well~ that makes sense~! But summer, pool, singing... they match perfectly!
いいねいいね！あの夏フェスの曲やろうよ〜！ 水鉄砲とか持って、みんなでびしょびしょになりながら！！
Nice, nice! Let's do that summer festival song~! With water guns and all, getting completely soaked together!!
え？でもあれってエモい感じの 恋愛ソングじゃなかった……？
Huh? But wasn't that an emotional love song...?
それをわたし達なりに歌いあげるってことよ！
That means we're gonna sing it our own way!
フェスにぴったりの選曲だからね！
Because it's the perfect song choice for the festival!
それじゃあ…！終わらない夏にするぞーっ！！！
Alright then...! Let's make this an unforgettable summer~!!!
おー！！！！
Ohhhh!!!!
君と夏フェス
You and the Summer Fest
まだ照れ臭いあいつとフェスに
I made a promise to go to a music festival
行く約束をしたはいいけど
with a guy I'm still awkward around, but...
あまりのってたら引かれそう
If I get too into it, he might be turned off,
控えめに楽しむって決めたんだ
so I decided to keep it low-key and enjoy myself quietly.
でも私の大好きな
But when my favorite rock star
ロックスター真夏のステージで
takes the midsummer stage
スーツを着たロックスターもう
wearing a suit, I just...
我慢できない！
can't hold back anymore!
止まらないのは私の汗
What won't stop—is it my sweat,
それとも君への気持ち？
or my feelings for you?
滴り落ちてく恋心
My dripping love—
こぼれないようにすくってね
please scoop it up so it doesn't spill over.
止まらないのは夏への期待
What won't stop is my anticipation for summer.
忘れられない
This might turn into an
夏になるかも
unforgettable summer.
夏の日差しで焼け焦げそう
It feels like I'm scorching under the summer sun,
すべてがスローモーションになる
and everything is moving in slow motion.
他人の汗もどうでもよくて
I don't care about other people's sweat,
日差しの鬱陶しさも感じない
nor do I feel the annoyance of the glaring sun.
でも私の大好きなロックスター
But my favorite rock star...
ラストの曲終わり
As the last song ends,
ロックスター帰ってく
the rock star leaves the stage.
ライブが終わって我に返って
When the live concert ends and I come to my senses,
それから...
and then...
ずいぶん前のほうに来ちゃってたみたい
Looks like I'd ended up way near the front.
さっきまで二人がいた場所、もう違う景色
Where the two of us were standing earlier is now a completely different scene.
ああ、わたしやっちゃった
Ahh, I really did it this time...
本気だったのに
Even though I meant to be sensible...
うつむく私の隣に君が
As I look down, you come stand beside me.
わたしの目を見つめる君 時間が止まってるみたい
You gaze into my eyes; it feels like time has stood still.
少し笑って君はいう
Smiling slightly, you say,
「新しい君が見れたから
"I got to see a new side of you,
今日は本当に来て良かった」
so I'm really glad I came today."
照れ笑いの奥見えちゃいそうで
Feeling like you might see right through my shy smile,
私は焦って目をそらした
I panicked and looked away.
止まらないのは二人の恋だ
What won't stop is the love between us.
今年の夏よ
Oh, summer of this year,
終わらないでよ。
please don't end.
はぁ～～～～……遊んだ遊んだっ♪
Aah... We played and played so much!
もう、くたくた… で、結局なん〜も決まってないっていう（笑）
I'm completely exhausted... And in the end, we haven't decided a single thing (laughs).
制服、洗濯に出しちゃったし…… 今日の衣装、いつもの着替えしかないよ～
I sent my uniform to the laundry, so for today's outfit, I only have my usual spare clothes...
もうこのままの格好で何かやるしかないね～っ！
Well, we'll just have to do something in these outfits then!
でもさ、やっぱりわたしたちにできることって… 歌とダンス、かな～って思うんだよね～
But you know, I think what we can really do... is song and dance, right?
うん… 変に着飾らずに、“いつものわたしたち”を見せるのが一番かも
Yeah... without dressing up unnecessarily, showing "our usual selves" might be best.
よっし！じゃあ歌う曲決めようよ！！ ねねは……エモい感じがいいなっ！いつもと違う感じの！
Alright! Then let's choose the song to sing!! Nene wants... something with an emotional vibe! Something different from usual!
ポルカは～～恋愛ソングやってみたいなぁ♡
Polka wants... to try singing a love song~♡
ラミィは元気いっぱい！ 合いの手たっぷりの盛り上がるやつ！！
Lamy wants lots of energy! Something super hyped with plenty of call-and-response!!
歌詞がグッとくる系の曲もいいなぁ～
A song with lyrics that really touch your heart would be nice too~
まぁ、みんな好みがバラバラだしね〜
Well, everyone's tastes are all over the place~
でも全部は無理じゃない？
But isn't doing everything impossible?
いや、できる！！やってみなきゃ始まらないっ！
No, we can! We won't know unless we try!
まさか…全部やる気？
Don't tell me... you want to do all of them?
もちろん！どれか１つなんてもったいないでしょっ！全部やって良いのがあるのか考えよう！
Of course! Picking just one would be a waste! Let's try them all and see which ones work!
ちょっとは休憩入れさせてね…
At least let us take a short break...
だったらさ！各自、自分の部屋でやりたい曲をやっていこう！
In that case, let's each perform our chosen songs in our own rooms!
じゃあまずはねねからねっ！！この曲は〜〜…ねねは違う服でやる！
Then Nene will go first! For this song... Nene will wear a different outfit!
わかった！やろっか〜
Got it! Shall we get started?
今度こそ……これで出し物を決めるぞ〜！
This time for sure... let's decide on our performance with this!
じゃあ！やりか〜！ねね〜着替え終わった？
Alright! Let me do it! Nene, are you done changing?
オッケー！それじゃあ、いきま〜す！！
Okay! Here we go!!
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten already,
夏の木陰に座ったまま
sitting in the shade of summer,
氷菓を口に放り込んで 風を待っていた
popping ice pops into our mouths, waiting for the breeze.
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten already,
世の中の全部嘘だらけ
that everything in this world is full of lies,
本当の価値を二人で探しに行こうと笑ったこと
how we laughed and said we'd go search for true value together.
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So that we won't forget, so that it won't fade,
形に残るものが全てじゃないように
so that tangible things aren't everything.
言葉をもっと教えて 夏が来るって教えて
Tell me more words, tell me that summer is coming.
僕は描いてる 眼に映ったのは夏の亡霊だ
I'm drawing it—what was reflected in my eyes was a summer ghost.
風にスカートが揺れて 思い出なんて忘れて
My skirt swaying in the wind, forgetting all about memories,
浅い呼吸をする 汗を拭って夏めく
taking shallow breaths, wiping away sweat as summer unfolds.
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten already,
夏の木陰に座った頃
back when we sat in the shade of summer.
遠くの丘から顔出した雲があったじゃないか
Wasn't there a cloud peeking out over the distant hill?
君はそれを掴もうとして
You tried to reach out and grab it,
馬鹿みたいに空を切った手で
waving your hand foolishly through the air.
僕は紙に雲一つを書いて 笑って握って見せて
I drew a cloud on paper, laughed, and showed it to you in my hand.
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So that we won't forget, so that it won't fade,
歴史に残るものが全てじゃないから
because what remains in history isn't everything.
今だけ顔も失くして 言葉も全部忘れて
For now, losing even our faces, forgetting all of our words,
君は笑ってる 夏を待っている僕ら亡霊だ
you are smiling; we are ghosts waiting for summer.
心をもっと教えて 夏の匂いを教えて
Tell me more about your heart, tell me the scent of summer.
浅い呼吸をする
Taking shallow breaths.
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So that we won't forget, so that it won't fade,
心に響くものが全てじゃないから
because what resonates in the heart isn't everything.
言葉をもっと教えて さよならだって教えて
Tell me more words, tell me even how to say goodbye.
今も見るんだよ 夏に咲いている花に亡霊を
Even now I see it: ghosts in the flowers blooming in summer.
言葉じゃなくて時間を
Not words, but time;
時間じゃなくて心をもっと
not time, but the heart.
浅い呼吸をする 汗を拭って夏めく
Taking shallow breaths, wiping away sweat as summer unfolds.
夏の匂いがする
I smell the scent of summer.
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've forgotten already,
夏の木陰に座ったまま
sitting in the shade of summer...
氷菓子を口に放り込んで
I popped an ice pop into my mouth
風を待っていた
and waited for the wind.
土曜日は あえることが 当たり前になって
Meeting up on Saturdays has become second nature,
不安からの あの気持ちが 消えてちょっと寂しいの
and with those anxious feelings gone, I feel a bit lonely.
一生分のキスの回数すぐに超えちゃうよ
We'll soon exceed a lifetime's worth of kisses.
まだ少し まだもっと
Still a little, still even more...
特別でいたい ずっと
I want to stay special forever.
出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling from when we met until we started dating.
わかってる ふりなんて 100年後もいらない
Pretending to understand—I won't need that even in 100 years.
二人の合図が増えたって 大事なこと言おう
Even as our secret signals increase, let me say what's important.
夏の日の はじまりを 季節が変わっても 覚えてて
Remember the start of that summer day, even as seasons change.
月曜は あえないなら 次の日はどうって？
If we can't meet on Monday, how about the next day?
繰り返しの 言葉だって それをもっと言ってよね
Even if they're repeated words, say them to me more.
一回だけの キスのために すぐに会いに来た
I came to see you right away, just for a single kiss.
あのときの あの場所は 特別じゃないし
That time, that place wasn't anything special.
ずっと 出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's forever keep that feeling from when we met until we started dating.
素っ気ない ふりなんて かっこよくもないよ
Pretending to be indifferent isn't cool at all.
間違いないこと増えたって 幸せちょっと違う
Even as certainties increase, happiness feels a bit different.
夏の日の はじまりが 正しい 恋をほら 映してる
Look, the start of that summer day reflects a true love.
ずっと 出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let me keep that feeling from when we met until we started dating forever.
わかってる ふりなんて 100年後もいらない
Pretending to understand—I won't need that even in 100 years.
二人の合図が増えたって 大事なこと言おう
Even as our secret signals increase, let's say what's important.
夏の日の はじまりを 季節が変わっても 覚えてて
Remember the start of that summer day, even as seasons change.
ねぇ 歌うわ
Hey, I'm gonna sing.
そうよ あなたに
That's right, to you.
甘えたいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
I want to be spoiled, but it might be embarrassing.
願い事の呪文 ほら
Here's the spell for my wish...
ずっとこのまま時間が 止まらぬかもね
Time might not stop while staying like this forever.
止まらぬかもね
It might be unstoppable...
こういうのが恋なの
Is this what love is?
ドキドキ ドキーン
Pit-a-pat, booming heart!
しかもね
And what's more...
スキスキスキ
I love you, love you, love you!
昨日よりも・・・かもね
Even more than yesterday... maybe.
・・・かもね
...Maybe.
ねぇ 歌って
Hey, sing for me.
そうよ あなたも
That's right, you too.
乙女の気持ちが 伝わるといいな
I hope a maiden's feelings reach you.
のどから出そうなくらい もう ラブラブラブ〜
About to burst out from my throat, so lovey-dovey~
ずっとこのまま あなた 素敵がいいな
Just like this forever, I hope you stay wonderful.
こういうのははじめて ドキドキ ドキーン
This is my first time feeling like this, pit-a-pat!
あぁ いいな スキスキスキ
Ah, it's so nice, I love love love you!
さっきよりも・・・いいな
Even more than a moment ago... so nice.
神様のヒマ潰し
[Title: Killing Time for God]
いつだって 新しいことに
Always fascinated by new things...
君は心 奪われてるから
...because your heart keeps getting captivated.
クルクルと 変わる
Changing round and round...
お天気 謎だらけ
...like the weather, full of mysteries.
いつだって TVをつけても
Whenever I turn on the TV...
知りたいことは 1つもないよ
...there isn't a single thing I want to know.
似たような ウワサ
Just similar rumors...
似たような ウワサばかり 謎がない
...filled with similar rumors, lacking any mystery.
手に入れたいんだ 君の 心の地図
I want to get my hands on the map of your heart.
Ah 探し当てたい 宝物の在処
Ah, I want to locate where your treasure lies.
その心の奥を掴んで 揺さぶるものは何？
What is it that grabs the depths of your heart and shakes it?
考えてるだけで 日が暮れる
Just thinking about it, the sun sets.
苦しくて 切なくて 楽しくて 日が暮れる
Painful, heartbreaking, yet fun—and the sun sets.
勘ぐって ありえない 想像
Overthinking, imagining impossible things...
へこんだかと思えば 笑ったり
...feeling down one moment, then laughing the next.
あたしはあたしで
As for me, in my own way...
相当 謎だらけ
...I'm full of mysteries myself.
ハマッてしまったら 恋は迷路
Once you fall into it, love is a maze.
Ah 角を曲がれば 行き止まりばかり
Ah, turn a corner, and it's dead ends everywhere.
物語の鍵を握って 遊んでいるのは誰？
Who is holding the key to the story and playing around?
ずいぶん悪趣味な ヒマ潰し
Such a bad-tasted pastime...
退屈しのぎに遊ぶ 神様の ヒマ潰し
Playing just to kill boredom—God killing time.
このところの
Lately, during these...
不安な夜は
...anxious nights,
胸の奥の奥の
deep, deep inside my chest,
チリチリと鳴き通す
it keeps throbbing with pain.
Ah 会えない理由はわかってるのに
Ah, even though I know the reason we can't meet...
物語の鍵を握って遊んでいるのは誰？
Who is playing around holding the key to the story?
ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
What a terrible way to kill time.
その心の奥を掴んで揺さぶるものは何？
What is grabbing and shaking the depths of that heart?
考えているだけで日が暮れて
Just thinking about it, the day comes to an end,
苦しくて切なくて楽しくて日が暮れる
painful, agonizing, yet fun, the day sets,
苦しくて切なくてこの恋に明け暮れる
painful and agonizing, I spend my days lost in this love.
つっ……疲れた～～！！
I'm... so tired!!
さすがに…全員分連続は応えたね…
Doing everyone's solos in a row really took it out of us...
でもでもっ！どの曲もサイコーだった～～！
But still! Every song was so awesome!!
うん…でも、“わたしたちらしさ”があるかって言われると…ちょっと悩むな～
Yeah... but if you ask whether it felt 'like us'... I'm a bit unsure~
まもなく、学寮祭が始まります。関係する生徒の皆さんは、速やかに準備をお願いします。
The Academy Dorm Festival will begin shortly. Participating students, please prepare promptly.
やっ、やば〜い！！もう始まっちゃうっては〜〜っ！
O-Oh no!! It's about to start already!!
え～～お腹すいた～～ちょっと購買行ってくるねっ！！
Ehh~ I'm hungry~ I'm gonna go to the store real quick!!
じゃ、わたしも行く～～♪
Then I'll go too~
ラミィも行く～～！
Lamy is coming too~!
えぇ～～！？ちょっと～～！？
Ehh~!? Wait a minute~!?
パン残ってるかな～～……ん？あれって……なんだ？？
I wonder if there's any bread left~ ...Hmm? What is... that??
こ、これは！
T-This is!
もしかして……！
Could it be...!
もしかしなくても！
No 'could it be' about it!
間違いないっ！！！
There's no mistake!!!
ねぽらぼ アニバーサリー パレード！
NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade!
ねぽらぼ5周年グッズがこんなところにー！
The NePoLaBo 5th Anniversary merch is right here!
きっと今日の配信終わりにラジオ出るやつだ！
This must be what's getting announced after today's stream!
気になる～！
I'm so curious~!
これは順番に見ていくしかないでしょう！
We've got to check them out one by one!
まずは、プレミアムアクリル色紙！
First up, the Premium Acrylic Shikishi!
今回のグッズのテーマが「花鳥風月」！
The theme for this set of merch is 'Kachou Fuugetsu'!
七原しえさんが描いてくれました！
It was illustrated by Shie Nanahara-san!
ねねたちの和服姿、綺麗でしょう～？
Look at us in our kimonos, isn't it beautiful~?
アクリル色紙にはねねたちの複製サインとロゴが入ってます！
The acrylic shikishi features our printed signatures and logo!
アクリルの脚もついてるから、机に飾っておくこともできるよ～！
It comes with acrylic stands, so you can display it on your desk~!
めっちゃ可愛いので、ぜひ！
It's super cute, so definitely get one!
次～！
Next~!
続いては、オフィシャルホロカスリーブ アニバーサリーパレードねぽらぼバージョン！
Next up, the Official HoloCard Sleeves: Anniversary Parade NePoLaBo Version!
もちろん、ホロカが入るスリーブです！
Of course, these sleeves fit HoloCards!
1パック60枚入ってるから、これでねぽらぼデッキを作り上げてください！
There are 60 cards per pack, so build your ultimate NePoLaBo deck with this!
いや、もう最近はね、ねぽらぼ全員で出ちゃいましたからね！
I mean, all of NePoLaBo got included recently!
もうこれでね、お前のオリジナルのデッキ構築をして、優勝していくんだ！
So build your own original deck with these and go win!
さあ、お前ならできる！やるしかない！
Come on, you can do it! You've got no choice!
見ているお前ら！ねぽらぼリスナー！お前ら頑張ってくれー！
Everyone watching! NePoLaBo listeners! Do your best!
次ー！
Next!
続いては、アクリルスタンド！
Next up, the Acrylic Stands!
プレミアムアクリル色紙とは別表情のラミィたちのアクリルスタンドです！
These acrylic stands feature different facial expressions from the premium acrylic shikishi!
花鳥風月で、花・春が桃鈴ねね
For Kachou Fuugetsu: Flower/Spring is Momosuzu Nene,
鳥・秋が獅白ぼたん
Bird/Autumn is Shishiro Botan,
風・夏が尾丸ポルカ
Wind/Summer is Omaru Polka,
月・冬が雪花ラミィとなっています！
and Moon/Winter is Yukihana Lamy!
では、次！
Now, next!
最後は、記念メダル！専用のケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルです！
Finally, the Commemorative Medals! They come with a special case and pouch!
それぞれタレントカラーと名前が入っていて、期生ごとにデザインが違うので、コレクションアイテムとしてぜひ揃えてみてください！
Each features the member's image color and name, with unique designs, so be sure to collect them all!
以上、ねぽらぼ アニバーサリーパレードのグッズでした！
And that concludes the NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade merchandise!
それでは――これより、学寮祭を開始いたします
And now... we will begin the dormitory festival.
ご来場の皆様、どうぞ最後までお楽しみください
To all our guests, please enjoy until the very end.
やばい！学寮祭始まるって！
Oh crap! The dorm festival is starting!
ねねたちも行かなきゃ！
We've gotta go too!
結局、何も買えなかったんだけど！
We didn't end up buying anything, though!
仕方ない。戻って学寮祭の話をしますか…
Can't be helped. Shall we go back and talk about the dorm festival...?
で？これは…何をしているの？？
So... what are we doing here??
ねねたちには、歌とダンスしかないっ！！ならばギリギリまで、全力で練習するしかないでしょー！！
All we have is singing and dancing! In that case, we have to practice with all our might until the very last second!!
もうお客さん入っているけどね(笑)
Though the audience is already coming in, you know. (laughs)
あぁあっ、もうやるしかないっ！！
Aaah, we just have to do this!!
でもさ…肝心の「何やるか」決めてないのでは？
But wait... haven't we not decided on the main thing: what we're actually going to do?
……でもさ、お客さんたちが見たいのって「やっぱり”わたし達らしさ”」だよね
...But you know, what the audience wants to see is ultimately 'our true selves', right?
それなら……オリ曲じゃない？
In that case... shouldn't it be our original songs?
じゃあ、全部やろう！！
Then let's do all of them!!
また～～～！？！？
Again~~~?!?!
１つだけじゃダメダメっ！衣装もぜーんぶ着替えて、たくさん歌おうよ！！
Just one isn't enough! Let's change into ALL our outfits and sing a ton of songs!!
メドレーってこと！？いいじゃんそれ！！
You mean a medley?! That sounds awesome!!
おぉ～～、いいかも！
Ooh~~, that might be good!
で、順番はどうするの？？
So, what about the order??
そんなんパッションでどうにかなるなるっ！！
We can figure that out on pure passion!!
こりゃ大変なことになりそうですね…
This looks like it's gonna turn into quite a mess...
ししろん？どうしたの？？
Shishiron? What's wrong??
……いや、何か忘れている気がするんだけど…思い出せない…
...Nah, I feel like we're forgetting something... but I can't place it...
大丈夫大丈夫大丈夫っ！これを歌えば学寮祭は、ねねたちのものっ！！
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine! Once we sing this, the dorm festival will be ours!!
よっしゃいくぞー！！
Alright, let's go!!
“わたし達らしさ”見せるよ！
We'll show them 'our true selves'!
うんっ！とりあえず、やるだけやろう！せーのっ！
Yep! For now, let's just do our best! Ready, set...
ねぽらぼメドレー！！
Nepolabo Medley!!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
To our future, illuminated by light
始めようか さあ Diving
Shall we start? Now, diving
待っても意味ない Timing
Waiting won't do any good, timing
でもたまに止まって Thinking Thinking
But sometimes stop and keep thinking, thinking
変えてみせる Change
I'll show you I can change
踏み出すのさ Stepping
Step forward, stepping
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ My Dream
I'll grab hold of my sparkling dream
叶う日まで Story 繋ぐから
I'll keep connecting the story until the day it comes true
だって君に ずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching me forever
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, together, everybody
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so it resounds
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
To our future, illuminated by light
Hyper Jumpin' Now
子どもくらい はしゃぐ方がお徳でしょ
It's better to make a fuss like kids, isn't it?
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
Tension crawling up from low pressure
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating speed just like this
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies ahead where we arrive
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Unstoppable feelings gaining a running start
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さぁ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin', let's jump around
ハイになって灰になるまで ダンシング Shake it up
Dancing and shaking it up until we get high and turn to ash
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Woh...
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to throb
Woh...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Disは No No
Dissing is No No
好きなら More More More
If you like it, More More More
邪魔するノイズは 撃ち消せ Bang Bang Bang
Shoot away the bothering noise, Bang Bang Bang
遊びたいだけ
Just wanna play
アンチは無視して
Ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴飛ばせ Kick it !!
Kick it away, Kick it !!
Jump Around!! Hyper Jumpin' Now
Cosmic Wonderful Tour!
一歩目がすでに異空間
The first step is already an alternate dimension
キラリ 渦に巻き込まれた？
Sparkling, were we swallowed into a vortex?
違うよ 出会いたくって
No, it's because we wanted to meet you
ホラ みんな ここにいる
Look, everyone is right here
夢のようで だけどね
It's like a dream, but you know...
ファンタジーじゃない感
...it feels like it's not a fantasy!
流星群 負けないよう
So we won't lose to a meteor shower,
光放って！
shine bright!
どんな憧れも飛び越えて
Surpassing any dream we longed for,
銀河の真ん中 行進しよう
let's march right through the center of the galaxy!
キラめきのシンフォニーさ
It's a sparkling symphony!
足跡だって星になる
Even our footprints turn into stars!
1, 2, 3 Yeah! 奇跡散りばめ
1, 2, 3 Yeah! Scattering miracles,
1, 2, 3 Yeah! 何万光年を
1, 2, 3 Yeah! Across tens of thousands of light-years!
1, 2, 3 Yeah! 旅していく季節が今
1, 2, 3 Yeah! The season of traveling on...
始まっんだよきっと！
...has surely begun!
せーの！ Wonderful Tour!
One, two, go! Wonderful Tour!
Wonderful Tour!
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reaching out to you, a melody of stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing our feelings tight, tight inside,
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
this harmony we play together with you...
これからもずっと続いてく
...will keep going on forever and ever!
Twinkle 4 You
ねぇねぇ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come closer!
回り始めた世界で踊らない？ 終わらない
Won't you dance in this world that's started spinning? It won't end!
わくわく 魔法かけたら
If we cast an exciting spell,
ドキドキはSyncしてほら Party Time 止まらない
heartbeats sync up, look, Party Time won't stop!
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Making a wish
Twinkle Twinkle 夜空で歌いましょう
Twinkle Twinkle, let's sing under the night sky!
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resonate to you, a melody of stars
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a brand new constellation
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony we play together with you...
これからもずっと続いてく
...will keep going on forever and ever!
Twinkle 4 You
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resonate to you, a melody of stars
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a brand new constellation
君と繋がっているこの宇宙に 宝石を散りばめよう
Let's scatter jewels across this sky that connects with you!
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reaching out to you, a melody of stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing our feelings tight, tight inside,
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
this harmony we play together with you...
これからもずっと続いてく
...will keep going on forever and ever!
La La La La...
やっぱ、ねほろぼだな〜！！
As expected of NePoLaBo~!!
これで学寮祭は大成功〜！！
With this, the Academy Dorm Festival is a huge success~!!
う〜ん……
Mmm...
えっ、ししろん？ どうしたの？
Eh, Shishiron? What's wrong?
いやさ……確かに良かったんだけど……なんかこう……何かを忘れてる気がするんだよね
Well... it was definitely great, but... I don't know, I feel like we forgot something.
なあに言ってんの！？ このメドレーで完璧だってば！
What are you talking about?! I'm telling you, this medley was absolute perfection!
そうだよ〜！ これでみーんな、ひとつになってハッピー！！
That's right~! Now everyone became as one and is super happy!!
来てくれた人たちも、きっとラミィたちの“声”を聴いて、喜んでくれたよ！
The people who came were surely happy hearing all of our voices too!
ひとつ……声……あっ！！！
As one... voice... Ah!!!
私たち、新曲作ってたじゃん！！！
We had made a new song, didn't we?!!!
あっ…
Ah...
わすれてたぁーーーー！！！
We totally forgot----!!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのにっ！！
And we practiced so much for it, too!!
Even though we practiced so hard!!
作ったのはいいけど……「出すタイミングどうしよう」って言ってたら、
Making it was great and all, but while we were discussing when to reveal it...
完全に忘れてた……
...we completely forgot about it...
出すタイミング絶対にここだったな〜
This was definitely the moment to reveal it~
もうステージ真っ暗だし〜〜〜！
The stage is already pitch black~~~!
……お客さん……まだいてくれてる、かな……
...I wonder... if the audience is still here with us...
……大丈夫！ 今なら、まだ——ギリギリ間に合う！！
...It's okay! If it's right now, we can still make it just in time!!
ねぇ！そこの君！！ まだ……見てくれてるよね？
Hey! You over there!! You're still... watching us, right?
ねねたちの、新しい曲——聞いてくれる？
Will you listen to our new song?
うん、うん…… きっと、聞いてくれるって信じてる！
Yeah, yeah... I'm sure everyone will listen, I believe it!
最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's get hyped together until the very end!
それでは——改めて…………んっ…… 聞いてください——ねぼらぼの新曲です
Well then—once again... *ahem*... Please listen to NePoLaBo's new song!
この先、みんなとなら、どこまでも行けると願って——歌います
Hoping that with everyone, we can go anywhere from here on—we sing.
5周年——その先の未来もずっと 一緒に見守り…歩んでください
5th anniversary... Please watch over us and walk alongside us for the future ahead.
1人じゃ辿り着けない場所へ… みんなで——
To a place we couldn't reach alone... Together with everyone—
ひとつになる声
Voices becoming one!
暗闇の中で 見つけた声
A voice found in the darkness
そのしるべを 辿りながら 僕らは 走るよ
Following that signpost, we run forward
ひとりぼっちだった日
The days when I was all alone
先が見えなかった日
The days when I couldn't see ahead
だけど君と出会えて
But after meeting you
そっと 扉を開けた
I gently opened the door
手のひらの中に また1を足して
Adding another step into the palm of my hand
何度も 奇跡を叶えよう
Let's make miracles come true time and time again
澄み渡る空の彼方
Beyond the clear blue sky
太陽と踊る 羽になる
Becoming wings that dance with the sun
情熱が突き動かす 僕らの明日を 照らして
Driven by passion, illuminate our tomorrow
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは
Running toward the same dream, we
強く心を結んで
Connect our hearts strongly
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
Because we can go anywhere, to the ends of the earth
これからまた続いてく道
The road that continues from here on
1人じゃ辿り着けない
Is a place I can't reach alone
だから この背中預けるよ
So I'll entrust my back to you
信じている 君の手を
I believe in your hand
僕らの未来を
In our future
みんなの声
Everyone's voices
君らしいって思う
I think, "That's so like you"
その積み重ねが
All those accumulated moments
なぜか嬉しくなるの
Make me feel happy for some reason
きっとこれからもそう
I'm sure it will be that way from now on too
手のひらの中の 大切な日々が
The precious days held in the palm of my hand
沢山の光を奏でて
Play countless lights
君と笑った
And I laughed with you
始まりの時の願い
The wish from the very beginning
今もほら輝いてる
Look, it's still shining now
未来まで連れてゆこう
Let's carry it forward into the future
暗闇を抜けた先に
Beyond the darkness
みんなの笑顔 見つけた
I found everyone's smiling faces
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは
Running toward the same dream, we
強く心を結んで
Connect our hearts strongly
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
Because we can go anywhere, to the ends of the earth
これからまた続いてく道
The road that continues from here on
1人じゃ辿り着けない
Is a place I can't reach alone
だから この背中預けるよ
So I'll entrust my back to you
信じている 君の手を
I believe in your hand
僕らの未来を
In our future
みんなの声を ひとつに
Bringing everyone's voices together as one
ひとつに
As one...
みんなの声を
...joining everyone's voices.
重ねて
Layering...
みんなの声を
...everyone's voices.
ひとつに
As one...
みんなの声を
...joining everyone's voices.
重ねて
Layering...
みんなの声を
...everyone's voices.
ひとつに 心合わせて
As one, uniting our hearts...
重ねて 僕らは願う
...and layering them, we make a wish.
ひとつに 光の中で
As one, inside the light...
重ねて ひとつになる声
...layering our voices until they become one!